- Why?
- Really, don't.
Hot-air blowers are incubators
and spewers of bacteria and pestilence.
It'd be more hygienic
if they had a plague-infested gibbon...
(Sheldon:)...sneeze my hands dry.
(Raj(entering excitedly):)Hey, guys.
I just got the most amazing new...
(Penny:)Do you think you'll ever be able to talk
in front of me without being drunk?
Okay, well, I'll just go eat by myself.
(Leonard:)- You don't have to do that.
- It's okay.
Between him not talking,
him talking, and him...
(Penny:)...I'm better off alone.
So goodbye, you poor, strange little man.
- She's so considerate.
- So, what's your news?
Remember that little object
I spotted beyond the Kuiper belt?
Oh, yeah, 2008-NQ sub-17.
Or as I call it, Planet Bollywood.
(Raj:)Anyway, because of my discovery...
(Raj:)...People magazine is naming me
one of their 30 Under 30 to Watch.